Guide to the Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-1553
  - Housing - physical problems with units, 1967-1971 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 7)
  - Housing policies, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 8)
  - Housing and Dining complaints, 1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 9)
  - Housing plans, 1969-1970 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 10)
  - Housing and Dining - Jack Shaw correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 11)